<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:sparkle="http://www.andymatuschak.org/xml-namespaces/sparkle" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Maccy</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/p0deje/Maccy/sparkle/appcast.xml</link>
    <description>Most recent changes with links to updates.</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>0.10.0</title>
      <description>
        <![CDATA[
          <h4>⚠️ This release (again) changes the storage system of history. Once upgraded, your new copies won't be visible to older versions of Maccy.</h4>
          <ul>
            <li>Migrated history storage from UserDefaults to CoreData for better performance and easier maintenance </li>
            <li>Added preferences windows which can be used to customize every aspect of the application behavior</li>
            <li>Added support for PNG image copies which is used by default macOS screenshotting tool</li>
            <li>Added support for different positioning of popup controlled by <code>popupPosition</code> option
              <ul>
                <li><code>cursor</code> which popups at pointer coordinates (default behavior)</li>
                <li><code>center</code> which popups at the center of the current screen</li>
                <li><code>statusItem</code> which popups in middle of menu icon (similar to what you'd have if you click on the icon manually)</li>
              </ul>
            </li>
            <li>Added possibility to add/remove custom pasteboard types from the ignored list using <code>ignoredPasteboardTypes</code> option</li>
            <li>Added support for <kbd>CONTROL (^)</kbd> + <kbd>W</kbd> keybinding which removes last word in search field</li>
            <li>Added better handling of global hotkey when using Dvorak keyboards</li>
            <li>Changed clearing behavior to keep pinned items by default. You can still clear all including pinned by selecting "Clear" with <kbd>OPTION (⌥)</kbd> pressed</li>
            <li>Added Spanish localization</li>
            <li>Added Russian localization</li>
            <li>Improved performance for large copies (100k+ characters)</li>
            <li>Fixed an issue when old pinned items would be removed when the storage size limit is reached</li>
          </ul>
        ]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>2020-06-03</pubDate>
      <releaseNotesLink>https://github.com/p0deje/Maccy/releases/tag/0.10.0</releaseNotesLink>
      <sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>10.13</sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>
      <enclosure
        url="https://github.com/p0deje/Maccy/releases/download/0.10.0/Maccy.app.zip"
        sparkle:version="0.10.0"
        length="0"
        type="application/octet-stream"
      />
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
