<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:sparkle="http://www.andymatuschak.org/xml-namespaces/sparkle" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Maccy</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/p0deje/Maccy/master/appcast.xml</link>
    <description>Most recent changes with links to updates.</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>2.0.0</title>
      <description>
        <![CDATA[
          <h4>Maccy 2.0 - the biggest release in 7 years!</h4>
          <p>Read more at <a href="https://github.com/p0deje/Maccy/discussions/790">https://github.com/p0deje/Maccy/discussions/790</a>.</p>

          <h5>Highlights of 2.0</h5>
          <ul>
            <li>The user interface has been rewritten from AppKit + NSMenu to SwiftUI + NSPanel.</li>
            <li>Storage has been rewritten from Core Data to SwiftData.</li>
            <li>Requires macOS 14 Sonoma or newer.</li>
            <li>Backward compatibility with Maccy 1.x. You can downgrade to 1.0 if you don't like the new version or encounter bugs.</li>
            <li>No backward compatibility with Maccy０.x.</li>
            <li>New setting to pop up at the last position Maccy was opened at (#829).</li>
            <li>New search highlight matches mode with a yellow color similar to Safari (#830).</li>
            <li>Improved memory usage for copying large images.</li>
            <li>Fixed multiple issues with Japanese/Chinese/Korean language input in search.</li>
            <li>Fixed an issue when Maccy could not be shown over password fields.</li>
            <li>Fixed an issue when Maccy would not paste to the Spotlight window.</li>
            <li>Fixed an issue when Maccy would not open over full-screen windows.</li>
          </ul>

          <h5>Differences from 1.0</h5>
          <ul>
            <li>The window can be resized like any other window and the history list is now scrollable.</li>
            <li>Pinned items are shown without dots and stick to the scrollable history list.</li>
            <li>Appearance preference <b>Number of items</b> removed. Instead, vertically resize the main panel window according to your needs.</li>
            <li>Appearance preference <b>Title length</b> removed. Instead, horizontally resize the main panel window according to your needs.</li>
            <li>Advanced preference <b>Avoid taking application focus</b> removed. The focus will always remain on the active application, similar to how Spotlight works.</li>
            <li>A pin letter "V" can no longer be used since it's reserved for a system paste shortcut.</li>
          </ul>

        ]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>2024-09-16</pubDate>
      <releaseNotesLink>https://github.com/p0deje/Maccy/releases/tag/2.0.0</releaseNotesLink>
      <sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>14.0</sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>
      <enclosure
        url="https://github.com/p0deje/Maccy/releases/download/2.0.0/Maccy.app.zip"
        sparkle:version="46"
        sparkle:shortVersionString="2.0.0"
        length="0"
        type="application/octet-stream"
      />
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
