<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:sparkle="http://www.andymatuschak.org/xml-namespaces/sparkle" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Maccy</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/p0deje/Maccy/sparkle/appcast.xml</link>
    <description>Most recent changes with links to updates.</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>0.9.0</title>
      <description>
        <![CDATA[
          <h4>⚠️ This release changes the storage way of history. Once upgraded, you won't be able to use older versions of Maccy without removing all your history.</h4>
          <ul>
            <li>Added support for pinned history items. Any history item can be pinned and unpinned using <kbd>OPTION (⌥)</kbd> + <kbd>P</kbd>.</li>
            <li>Added support for storing, viewing, copying and pasting images.</li>
            <li>Added support for transient copies which is used by various apps to copy sensitive data like passwords. Maccy now ignores such copies and not store them in history.</li>
            <li>Added support for different sorting algorithms of history which are controlled by <code>sortBy</code> option:
              <ul>
                <li><code>lastCopiedAt</code> sorts items by the time the item was last copied (default behavior)</li>
                <li><code>firstCopiedAt</code> sorts items by the time the item was first copied</li>
                <li><code>numberOfCopies</code> sorts items by the total number of times the item was copied</li>
              </ul>
            </li>
            <li>Added an option to completely hide the footer items (Clear, About, Quit, etc.) by setting <code>hideFooter</code> to <code>true</code>.</li>
            <li>Added an option to popup window in the center of the screen by setting <code>popupPosition</code> to <code>center</code>.</li>
            <li>Fixed a bug when multiple copies issued by the same app like BBEdit would not be handled correctly.</li>
            <li>Fixed a bug when clearing the history during the search would crash.</li>
          </ul>
        ]]>
      </description>
      <pubDate>2020-03-15</pubDate>
      <releaseNotesLink>https://github.com/p0deje/Maccy/releases/tag/0.9.0</releaseNotesLink>
      <sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>10.13</sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>
      <enclosure
        url="https://github.com/p0deje/Maccy/releases/download/0.9.0/Maccy.app.zip"
        sparkle:version="0.9.0"
        length="0"
        type="application/octet-stream"
      />
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
